<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ireland on Independent.ie</title>
    <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//categories/ireland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ireland on Independent.ie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 13:07:31 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="username.github.io/myprojectname//categories/ireland/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallout from Trump&#39;s US tax reforms is a reality Irish business must grasp</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/tax/</guid>
      <description>It is now probable that major reform of the US tax system will be enacted before the end of 2017. Nearly 1,000 pages of tax legislation are now being considered and working their way through the US legislative process at an almost unprecedented pace. These are significant proposals, which will undoubtedly have a wide-ranging impact on all US business and individuals. What is also becoming clear is that US tax reform as proposed has a global reach with knock-on implications for US companies operating in Ireland and Irish companies doing business in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tubridy &#39;moved to tears&#39; at Toy Show rehearsals</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/christmas/</guid>
      <description>More than 500 gizmos and gadgets, 285 children and around 15 Christmas jumpers will feature in tonight&amp;rsquo;s Toy Show.
Ryan Tubridy will tonight host the eagerly-awaited show, which is this year inspired by Beauty And The Beast.
The presenter believes that it&amp;rsquo;s all about its young stars.
&amp;ldquo;I saw the rehearsal today and I was moved to tears with this brother and sister act that do something tomorrow,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;I think tomorrow night is going to be about kids more than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ikea not planning new stores in Ireland as sales hit €167m</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/ikea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 15:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/ikea/</guid>
      <description>Ikea&amp;rsquo;s store in Ballymun is as busy as some of the Swedish group&amp;rsquo;s biggest international stores in places such as Russia and New York, with more than 3.6 million visits paid to the Dublin outlet in the last financial year. The Ikea store is ranked number two among all its global outlets for home decoration sales, and number three for lighting sales. But despite the huge number of visits paid to the store, Ikea Ireland&amp;rsquo;s market manager, Claudia Marshall, said there are still no public plans to open any other outlets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dublin Terror Attack</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/garda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 15:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/garda/</guid>
      <description>It could take the Army up to two hours to deploy specialist soldiers to Dublin in the event of a terrorist attack. The Sunday Times reports that the Army Ranger Wing, based in the Curragh in Kildare, does not have 24-hour access to helicopters. Those that are available can only transport a small number of fully equipped soldiers at a time. Gardaí and Defence Forces took part in a training exercise in the capital during the week, but response times for the rest of the country have not yet been tested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow And Freezing Temperatures Predicted For The Weekend</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/weather/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to rethink that Christmas party outfit.
If you&amp;rsquo;re heading out to get into the festive swing of things this weekend you&amp;rsquo;ll need to wrap up warm because snow and freezing cold temperatures are being forecast for the next few days.
  Guardian News on Youtube.
According to Met Eireann there will be wintry showers right across the country with accumulations of snow over northern areas.
There will also be ground frost with with icy patches and lows of minus 2 degrees, staying coldest over the eastern half of the country.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
