<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Independent.ie</title>
    <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Independent.ie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 16:56:43 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="username.github.io/myprojectname//post/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Brexit Deal</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/brexit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 16:56:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/brexit/</guid>
      <description>Theresa May’s hopes of securing a unique post-Brexit trade deal with the EU were under threat on Saturday night as Brussels said it was coming under international pressure to deny Britain special treatment.
After a week that saw May reach a deal with the EU that will allow Brexit talks to move forward on to future trade relations, EU officials insisted a bespoke deal more favourable to the UK than other non-EU nations was out of the question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildfires devastate southern California</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/wildfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/wildfire/</guid>
      <description>Nearly 200,000 residents have been evacuated from their homes in California as firefighters battle several raging wildfires. Governor Jerry Brown declared a state of emergency in San Diego on Thursday after a new blaze spread from 10 acres to 4,100 acres in just a few hours. Three firefighters have been injured and about 500 buildings destroyed. One death has been reported - a woman&amp;rsquo;s body was found in a burned-out area in Ventura County.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallout from Trump&#39;s US tax reforms is a reality Irish business must grasp</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/tax/</guid>
      <description>It is now probable that major reform of the US tax system will be enacted before the end of 2017. Nearly 1,000 pages of tax legislation are now being considered and working their way through the US legislative process at an almost unprecedented pace. These are significant proposals, which will undoubtedly have a wide-ranging impact on all US business and individuals. What is also becoming clear is that US tax reform as proposed has a global reach with knock-on implications for US companies operating in Ireland and Irish companies doing business in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tubridy &#39;moved to tears&#39; at Toy Show rehearsals</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/christmas/</guid>
      <description>More than 500 gizmos and gadgets, 285 children and around 15 Christmas jumpers will feature in tonight&amp;rsquo;s Toy Show.
Ryan Tubridy will tonight host the eagerly-awaited show, which is this year inspired by Beauty And The Beast.
The presenter believes that it&amp;rsquo;s all about its young stars.
&amp;ldquo;I saw the rehearsal today and I was moved to tears with this brother and sister act that do something tomorrow,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;I think tomorrow night is going to be about kids more than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars: The Last Jedi Premiere</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 15:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/movie/</guid>
      <description>John Boyega attended the Star Wars: The Last Jedi premiere on Saturday evening in Los Angeles, hours after tweeting about being delayed in Atlanta. The city received major snowfall on Friday morning, which led Boyega to tweet, &amp;ldquo;Wow ATL. Looks like no one&amp;rsquo;s leaving! Guess I&amp;rsquo;ll start a family now&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;
He then shared with his followers, &amp;ldquo;Trying to get back for the LA premiere! I actually NEED a pilot !!!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ikea not planning new stores in Ireland as sales hit €167m</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/ikea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 15:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/ikea/</guid>
      <description>Ikea&amp;rsquo;s store in Ballymun is as busy as some of the Swedish group&amp;rsquo;s biggest international stores in places such as Russia and New York, with more than 3.6 million visits paid to the Dublin outlet in the last financial year. The Ikea store is ranked number two among all its global outlets for home decoration sales, and number three for lighting sales. But despite the huge number of visits paid to the store, Ikea Ireland&amp;rsquo;s market manager, Claudia Marshall, said there are still no public plans to open any other outlets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dublin Terror Attack</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/garda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 15:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/garda/</guid>
      <description>It could take the Army up to two hours to deploy specialist soldiers to Dublin in the event of a terrorist attack. The Sunday Times reports that the Army Ranger Wing, based in the Curragh in Kildare, does not have 24-hour access to helicopters. Those that are available can only transport a small number of fully equipped soldiers at a time. Gardaí and Defence Forces took part in a training exercise in the capital during the week, but response times for the rest of the country have not yet been tested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Kardashian Makes Her Debut on Kardashian-Jenner Christmas Card</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/kardashian/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 15:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/kardashian/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Kardashian-Jenner Christmas card, Dream Kardashian!
Rob Kardashian&amp;rsquo;s 1-year-old baby girl makes her debut on the almost annual card, as revealed by his sister Kim Kardashian and mother Kris Jenner on Saturday. The family members have been unveiling parts of the 2017 Kardashian-Jenner Christmas card daily like a holiday advent calendar.
  Entertainment Tonight on Youtube.
Article from eonline.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johann van Graan responds to accusations from Leicester camp after thumping win</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/sportsnews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/sportsnews/</guid>
      <description>Munster coach Johann van Graan played down accusations from Leicester counterpart Matt O&amp;rsquo;Connor that his side were cynical at the breakdown during his side&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive 33-10 Champions Cup win at Thomond Park. A scintillating opening half-hour laid the basis for the win, tries from Rhys Marshall and Simon Zebo, aided by four successful Ian Keatley kicks, helping Munster build a 20-0 lead which rarely looked like being threatened.
  Munster Rugby on Youtube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow And Freezing Temperatures Predicted For The Weekend</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/weather/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to rethink that Christmas party outfit.
If you&amp;rsquo;re heading out to get into the festive swing of things this weekend you&amp;rsquo;ll need to wrap up warm because snow and freezing cold temperatures are being forecast for the next few days.
  Guardian News on Youtube.
According to Met Eireann there will be wintry showers right across the country with accumulations of snow over northern areas.
There will also be ground frost with with icy patches and lows of minus 2 degrees, staying coldest over the eastern half of the country.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
