<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aine Harte on Independent.ie</title>
    <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//author/aine-harte/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aine Harte on Independent.ie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 15:42:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="username.github.io/myprojectname//author/aine-harte/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars: The Last Jedi Premiere</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 15:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/movie/</guid>
      <description>John Boyega attended the Star Wars: The Last Jedi premiere on Saturday evening in Los Angeles, hours after tweeting about being delayed in Atlanta. The city received major snowfall on Friday morning, which led Boyega to tweet, &amp;ldquo;Wow ATL. Looks like no one&amp;rsquo;s leaving! Guess I&amp;rsquo;ll start a family now&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;
He then shared with his followers, &amp;ldquo;Trying to get back for the LA premiere! I actually NEED a pilot !!!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Kardashian Makes Her Debut on Kardashian-Jenner Christmas Card</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/kardashian/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 15:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/kardashian/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Kardashian-Jenner Christmas card, Dream Kardashian!
Rob Kardashian&amp;rsquo;s 1-year-old baby girl makes her debut on the almost annual card, as revealed by his sister Kim Kardashian and mother Kris Jenner on Saturday. The family members have been unveiling parts of the 2017 Kardashian-Jenner Christmas card daily like a holiday advent calendar.
  Entertainment Tonight on Youtube.
Article from eonline.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow And Freezing Temperatures Predicted For The Weekend</title>
      <link>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>username.github.io/myprojectname//post/weather/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to rethink that Christmas party outfit.
If you&amp;rsquo;re heading out to get into the festive swing of things this weekend you&amp;rsquo;ll need to wrap up warm because snow and freezing cold temperatures are being forecast for the next few days.
  Guardian News on Youtube.
According to Met Eireann there will be wintry showers right across the country with accumulations of snow over northern areas.
There will also be ground frost with with icy patches and lows of minus 2 degrees, staying coldest over the eastern half of the country.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
